In this exercise, you are asked to implement a function that visualizes a list of
images in a grid and displays color-coded bounding boxes using Matplotlib.
I started by reformatting
our ground_truth input to a dictionary to make the data more accessible.
I then created a Colormap, in this case,
a dictionary that maps each class ID to a RGB triplet.
We can use the subplots function in Matplotlib to create a grid.
We can loop through the different images to display them in the grid.
Using Matplotlib patches, we can display on each image,
the different bounding boxes using the Colormap we created.
Creating such visualization is extremely useful to better understand your data.